davedraper.com 2006-06-19

# IronOnline Privacy Policy

  |  |  | 

Dave Draper's IronOnline has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website. 

This site contains links to other sites. **davedraper.com** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

Our site uses an order form for customers to order products and services. We collect visitor's contact information (like their address) and financial information (like their credit card number). Contact information from the order form is used to send orders or to get in touch with them if necessary to fill their order. Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services. 

## Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Specifically, the credit card information is entered into our host's secure server and is never transferred via email.

## Children's Guidelines

Our IronOnline site meets the guidelines of TRUSTe's children's program. We do: 

  1. NOT collect online contact information without prior parental consent or parental notification, which will include an opportunity for the parent to prevent use of the information and participation in the activity. Without prior parental consent, online information will only be used to respond directly to the child's request and will not be used for other purposes without prior parental consent
  2. NOT collect personally identifiable offline contact information without prior parental consent
  3. NOT distribute to third parties any personally identifiable information with out prior parental consent
  4. NOT give the ability to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information without prior parental consent
  5. NOT entice by the prospect of a special game, prize or other activity, to divulge more information than is needed to participate in the activity

## Choice/Opt-Out

Your email address is used as a mailbox destination for our free weekly email newsletter, or to answer your submitted questions. 

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. 

  1. Un-subscribe instructions are found at the bottom of each weekly newsletter. 
  2. You can email Laree directly for assistance at [ldraper@davedraper.com](mailto:laree@davedraper.com)
  3. You can send mail to the following postal address:  P. O. Box 1335, Aptos, CA 95001
  4. You can call the following toll-free telephone number: 888-466-9185 
  5. You can send mail via FAX to 831-466-9183 

## Correct/Update

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. 

  1. Email [ldraper@davedraper.com](mailto:ldraper@davedraper.com)
  2. Send mail to the following postal address:  P. O. Box 1335, Aptos, CA 95001
  3. Call the following telephone number: 831-466-8182 
  4. You can also fax 831-466-8193 

## Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact 

Laree Draper Dave Draper's IronOnline P. O. Box 1335 Aptos, CA 95001 831-466-9182

|  |   
---  

Order and Shipping policy   
Privacy policy  
Contact us 

[  
](http://www.completerss.com/viewrss.aspx?rss=http://www.davedraper.com/davedraper.xml)**  
****BROTHER IRON SISTER STEEL**  
****A Bodybuilder's Book  
by Dave Draper, $24.95   
Well written and motivating ** **  
More Info **  
—** ******

****STELLA'S KITCHEN**  
**Simple Creative Cooking  
by Stella Juarez  
E-book, $19.95  
Fabulous reviews! **  
More Info**  
— 

**YOUR BODY REVIVAL**  

**Weight Loss Straight Talk  
by Dave Draper, $18.95  
The perfect diet book—all the information you need, plus the motivation to get the job done. **  
More Info **  
— 

TOTAL TRAINING 

**  
  
Weightlifter's Log, $11.95  
Coil bound.  
Click on the order link to download a sample page   
More Info ******
